<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>weekly on Joy&#39;s Personal Website</title>
    <link>https://joywang.co/tags/weekly/</link>
    <description>Recent content in weekly on Joy&#39;s Personal Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>me@example.com (joy)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>me@example.com (joy)</webMaster>
    <copyright>2021 Janne Kemppainen All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://joywang.co/tags/weekly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Week in Cryptography Research July 15</title>
      <link>https://joywang.co/2024/07/15/2024-07-07-this-week-in-crypto-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>me@example.com (joy)</author>
      <guid>https://joywang.co/2024/07/15/2024-07-07-this-week-in-crypto-research/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the fourth issue of the cryptography research (bi-)weekly! This week I took a look at an interesting construction on top of OpenID to ensure privacy of relying parties to identity providers. Another topic focuses on how to do remote attestation of devices more efficiently. Both leverage some commitment schemes as part of the constructions.
OPPID: Single Sign-On with Oblivious Pairwise Pseudonyms(Link) Single Sign-On (SSO) is a protocol that allows users to conveniently authenticate to many Relying Parties (RPs) through a central Identity Provider (IdP).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Week in Cryptography Research June 30</title>
      <link>https://joywang.co/2024/06/30/2024-06-30-this-week-in-crypto-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>me@example.com (joy)</author>
      <guid>https://joywang.co/2024/06/30/2024-06-30-this-week-in-crypto-research/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the third issue of the cryptography research weekly! This week I read about adaptor signature contruction and a technique for more efficient verification of multi-signatures.
Adaptor Signatures: New Security Definition and A Generic Construction for NP Relations(Link) I have read about adaptor signatures in Bitcoin land a while ago, this paper offered a generic construction that is not only particular to ECDSA or Schnorr.
An Adaptor signature scheme is defined based on a relation R where there is a signer and a receiver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Week in Cryptography Research June 22</title>
      <link>https://joywang.co/2024/06/22/2024-06-22-this-week-in-crypto-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>me@example.com (joy)</author>
      <guid>https://joywang.co/2024/06/22/2024-06-22-this-week-in-crypto-research/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the second issue of the cryptography research weekly! This week I read about randomness implementation considerations and encryption techniques.
VRaaS: Verifiable Randomness as a Service on Blockchains(Link) This paper provides a formalized framework for verifiable randomness that captures core features such as unbiasability, unpredictability, and public verifiability but also the onchain components design. The randomness requester first sends a request to smart contract and records a unique ID onchain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Week in Cryptography Research June 16</title>
      <link>https://joywang.co/2024/06/16/2024-06-16-this-week-in-crypto-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>me@example.com (joy)</author>
      <guid>https://joywang.co/2024/06/16/2024-06-16-this-week-in-crypto-research/</guid>
      <description>This is the augural issue for This Week in Cryptography Research. I hope to summarize 2 papers I read this week and highlight the main contributions. I focus on papers that are most interesting to me, and has a strong preference to practical applications and constructions over theories and attacks.
Atomic and Fair Data Exchange via Blockchain (Link) I came across this paper while reading about various data storage solutions related to the blockchain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
